http://members.tripod.com/delta10/privacy.html

Privacy Statement for
The David Connection
The David Connection
has created this privacy
statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses the information gathering and
dissemination practices for this Web site:
The David Connection
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to gather broad demographic information.
(** The David Connection does not personally gather information, however, signing the guestbook will result in demographic information being collected for no other purpose than to inform the guestbook owner from what parts of the country the visitors are from. **)
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies.
While we do not use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads may be
collected by the ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Personal Information
This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally
identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.Please note however that submitting a query into
the "Care to Make History" form will result in your mailing address being attatched to the form. This
information is also not shared with third parties.
Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal
information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites.
The David Connection
is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:
cjlrk@monisys.ca
Generated by Privacy Wizard
